{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tree Root Fertilization Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62557/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62557,"taskName":"Trees \u0026 Shrubs - Deep Root Fertilization","taskDescription":"Fertilize Trees and Shrubs","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tree Root Fertilization Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Trees Shrubs Treat fertilize fertilization feed","textMessagingName":"Tree Fertilize","rolloverLongDesc":"Feeding and fertilization of trees and shrubs often referred to as deep root fertilization.","rolloverShortDesc":"Fertilize, feeding, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Fertilize Tree and Shrub Roots.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated Deep Root Fertilization companies in your area.","htmlTitle":"Deep Root Fertilization \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fertilize Trees and Shrubs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":79,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Fertilize or Feed Trees and Shrubs","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Trees \u0026 Shrubs - Deep Root Fertilization","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Deep Root Fertilization Needs","urlName":"Deep-Root-Fertilization-Trees-Shrubs","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Tree \u0026 Shrub Deep Root Fertilization Services in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Trees Shrubs Treat fertilize fertilization feed, root","emcCategoryOid":-12074,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9202,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62557/":{"taskOID":62557,"originalTaskOID":62557,"setID":9202,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7182,"questionDisplayText":"# of Trees and Shrubs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many trees/shrubs are involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5213,"questionDisplayText":"Other Services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other services are you interested in? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8155,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and advise","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and advise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8156,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8157,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Basic maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Basic maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8159,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8160,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Trunk injection applications","answerDisplayText":"Trunk injection applications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pruning","answerDisplayText":"Pruning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8162,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7182,"questionDisplayText":"# of Trees and Shrubs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many trees/shrubs are involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5213,"questionDisplayText":"Other Services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other services are you interested in? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8155,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and advise","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and advise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8156,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8157,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Basic maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Basic maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8159,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8160,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Trunk injection applications","answerDisplayText":"Trunk injection applications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pruning","answerDisplayText":"Pruning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8162,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8155,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and advise","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and advise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8156,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8157,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Basic maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Basic maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8159,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8160,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Trunk injection applications","answerDisplayText":"Trunk injection applications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pruning","answerDisplayText":"Pruning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8162,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}